Whatever they dream up... he has to survive.
Bedtime Stories is a fantasy, comedy, family film directed by Adam Shankman.
Skeeter Bronson is a down-on-his-luck guy who's always
telling bedtime stories to his niece and nephew.
But his life is turned upside down when the fantastical stories he
makes up for entertainment inexplicably turn into reality.
Can a bewildered Skeeter manage his own unruly fantasies now that the outrageous characters
and situations from his mind have morphed into actual people and events?
Skeeter Bronson, played by Adam Sandler.
Jill, played by Keri Russell.
Kendall, played by Guy Pearce.
Wendy, played by Courteney Cox.
Aspen, played by Lucy Lawless.
Hot Girl, played by Carmen Electra.
Bedtime Stories is a 2008 American fantasy comedy film directed by Adam Shankman from
a screenplay by Matt Lopez and Tim Herlihy based on a story by Lopez.
It stars Adam Sandler in his first appearance in a family film, alongside Keri Russell, Guy Pearce, Aisha
Tyler, Russell Brand, Richard Griffiths, Teresa Palmer, Lucy Lawless, and Courteney Cox.
In the film, a hotel handyman's stories to his niece and nephew
come true, and his stories become more outlandish.
Sandler's production company Happy Madison Productions and Andrew Gunn's
company Gunn Films co-produced the film with Walt Disney Pictures.
The film premiered on December 25, 2008, by Disney.
Despite the film being a box office success, earning $212.9 million against an $80
million budget, it received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of wishes come true, escapade,
disorder, imaginary, miraculous event.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.